# Duplicated file so it's easier to import
quiz = {
    1: {
        "question": "Q1: \nThe Maori word for 'five'",
        "answer": "Rima"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "Q2: \nChristchurch's Maori name?",
        "answer": "Otautahi"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "Q3: \nMaori word for 'chicken'",
        "answer": "Heihei"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "Q4: \nCount to ten in Maori",
        "answer": "tahi rua toru wha rima ono whitu waru iwa tekau"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "Q5: \nTranslate 'rƒÅtapu' into english",
        "answer": "Sunday"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "Q6: \nTranslate 'rua tekau' into English (Use letters)",
        "answer": "Twenty"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "Q7: \nTranslate whanau into English",
        "answer": "Family"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "Q8: \nTranslate 'New Zealand' into English",
        "answer": "Aotearoa"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "Q9: \nMaori for 'Ocean'",
        "answer": "Moana"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "Q10: \n'One hundred' in maori?",
        "answer": "Kotahi rau"
    }}
